i'm tired it's all your guys fault that
we miss the school bus
now we have to walk all the way home
don't blame me it's manic and mindy's
fault for staying behind after school to
have sex in the bathroom hey sonia do
you know who hero brian is herobrine
herobrine is a ghost who haunts the
single-player worlds in minecraft he
looks like a standard steve
minecraft's original default player skin
but you'll know him by his white eyes
okay
me and sonic ran into him last night he
was really scary
okay manic can you not stand in front of
me i'm downwind and you're but crack
really stinks manic stop trying to tell
sonia about herobrine you know girls
find herobrine scary huh
sonic sonia look there's a broken beer
bottle on the ground
well hurry up and grab it so you can
give it to mindy tomorrow as a gift you
know she likes sticking foreign objects
up her ass
[Music]
sonia do you know what nether traveling
is
no is it another minecraft thing it's
when you build a lot of nether portals
in specific areas of another if you put
them in the right places you can travel
long distances hey ha i wish we could do
that in real life and fast travel all
the way home sonia shut up hey sibs i
know one way we could fast travel
how about we hop over that fence our
house is right over there manic no
you're always getting us into trouble or
some [ __ ] what if there is a homosexual
on that side of the fence and he tries
to rape you yeah bro i think climbing
into somebody's backyard is considered
trespassing also you guys are being
poopy baby [ __ ] it's only trespassing
if we get caught
i'm gonna climb over first don't stare
at my ass sibs come on now gunky poops
don't ask the impossible from your big
bro and big sis
come on sonic it's your turn
um i don't know about this you guys it's
a little high what if i fall and break
my ass bro your butt cheeks are like two
round bowling balls filled with jello i
don't think you could break it if you
tried
yeah don't be [ __ ] if anything your
squishy watermelon size butt cheeks will
cushion the blow
i still don't know maybe there's another
way around
yo big blue check it there's a hole in
the fence over here that you might be
able to fit through
whoa you're right i can totally fit
through this
make room [ __ ] cause i'm coming over
oh no you guys i think i'm stuck oh my
god i'm so fat i'm so embarrassed
stop it stop laughing at me stop it i'm
starting to feel so hungry so weak i'm
going to starve like this bro you've
only been stuck in there for 10 seconds
yeah but i'm still hungry make yourself
useful for once bro and go find me
something to eat
i guess i could look around by that tree
over there and find you some acorns
do i look like a squirrel bro you
[ __ ] [ __ ] i'm a hedgehog i need
substance up in this [ __ ] we could run
home real quick and grab a can of chef
boyardee oh yeah that sounds good do
that daddy needs that quality [ __ ] okay
we won't be gone for more than a couple
minutes
manic what are you looking at
i'm checking the sex offenders registry
for the neighborhood if we're going to
leave sonic here in such a vulnerable
position with his fat ass presenting on
the other side of the fence like a
glorified slab of steak we should take
precautions
uh
[Music]
see you in about 10 minutes bro
the oracle of delphius
oracle of delphius you live in that
house
yet i do
oh well you know that your house is
marked on the sex offenders registry
right
yeah i know
so uh where are your brother and sister
i saw them out here just a second ago
they ran home to get me something to eat
but they'll be back in a couple minutes
oh ha ha i see you know sonic i just
pulled a batch of chocolate chip cookies
out of the oven how about you come
inside and we can enjoy them together
nothing beats a fresh batch of cookies
and a big glass of my [ __ ] pee oh
whoops ha ha i meant to say milk i would
love to or a collab delphius but as you
can see i'm kinda stuck
oh would you look at that i didn't even
noticed you are stuck aren't you boy in
the position you are now nothing would
stop an old man from [ __ ] you in the
ass cheeks
um i guess
[Music]
how many times do we have to tell you to
leave the young ones alone old man
oracle of delphius what's going on back
there are you okay
oh it looks like bartel b is out on the
town for a nice stroll in his tight nice
fitting pair of khaki pants
bart levy bart levy my love can you come
over here and lend me your aid
[Music]
oh no he can't hear me because he's
listening to last resort with his new
state-of-the-art air boss
[Music]
man i'm bored maybe i should drive to
the other side of town and pick up the
hooker
to take home so my parents will stop
asking if i'm gay
well that guy is so beautiful
if i wasn't busy pretending to be
straight i wish i'll go over there and
ask him to spank me
hold up he looks kind of familiar have i
seen him somewhere
[Music]
that's it i knew i recognized him from
somewhere
that's him all right that's the
[ __ ] that killed my dad and
stole my graduation diploma in
kindergarten
i finally found him after so [ __ ]
long i'll eventually add
i'm gonna need some sick tunes for this
[ __ ]
oh yeah baby let's get this party
started
[ __ ] wrong one
oh no that car it's heading straight
towards bartleby and it's not stopping
hey can you hear me there's somebody in
the road you have to stop now or you are
going to die
my words aren't getting through to him
he's blasting his music too loud
does he not realize bartleby is going to
make him die
damn i have to [ __ ] pop
[Music]
bro sis you're back did you bring me the
goods of course anything for our bro
one serving of chef boyardee coming
right up
cheese ravioli but but i wanted
spaghettios
don't be a baby that's all they gave us
at the food pantry last wednesday
if you don't want it give it back that
was going to be dinner tonight anyway
nah it's fine i appreciate it sips you
didn't have to go get it for me but you
did
for that i am eternally grateful and in
your debt
i don't care you piss me off so i change
my mind
sorry bro
too late i play games on the xbox so i
don't know how to forgive people like
you do
hey i have an idea since he doesn't want
it why don't we try using it to get him
unstuck instead
elaborate
what i mean is why not use the ravioli
sauce as some kind of lubricant so he
can't slip out without trouble
or we can use my wet coop
or we can use chef boyardee
okay one of us is going to have to go
back behind the fence and given him a
push do you want to go or shall i you go
since i have a photographic memory i
don't want to look at sonic's big ass
butt
i'm climbing over i know my thick thighs
make me pretty bangable but you better
not be checking out my butt
don't move so much down there bro you're
going to make me fall i ain't doing [ __ ]
just pick up the speed gunky poops
stop it you know i hate when you call me
that
ah
now
manic you forgot about the cheese
ravioli
um yo knucklehead can a bro get a bite
of that dog
sonic what happened is barley back there
giving you a good time
ha ha ha ha ha
very funny hetero but if you must know
however i'm stuck and it's not because
i'm fat
wait a minute is that ketchup on a hot
dog disgusting
what are you four
big boys like us aren't supposed to put
ketchup on a hot dog
get out of my face you disgust me
shut your mouth [ __ ]
what do you think gives a man the right
to tell another man what he can and
can't put on his own weakness
so i'm your boyfriend
he's not hanging around here anywhere
i would think not
why do you ask
just so you know bartleby doesn't sign
autographs on tuesdays
because that's when he gets his
fingernails polished at the nail salon
for 29
438 bucks
good then nothing's stopping me from
doing this
sonja i can't reach it help me help your
big bro
justify your reason for being in this
family for once in your life
yum
oh
sister be honest with me am i fat
should i tell you the truth
the truth is all that i demand fool
you are just a little bit
[Music]
[Applause]
come on baby boy
[Music]
the sonic underground does it again
where would i be without my baby sibs
yes where indeed
bart levy where did you come from i
thought you were at the salon
i was i just got finished as you can
clearly see
that's good
how was your trip to the salon babe
why don't you tell me
no way is that real gold golden finger
nail polish
super cool
damn boy i see you
impressed this cost me 13 bucks
now i'm a long beach i bought a whopper
from burger king and it is so big i
simply cannot finish it myself will you
help me
oh boy would i
of course you would i honestly don't
even know why i bother asking [ __ ]
cut my life into pieces this is my last
resort suffocation no breathing don't
give a [ __ ]
this is
[Music]
losing my mind
[Applause]